Guide to the Time Inc. Time Research Center Files 1919-2015 MS 3009-RG 13
New-York Historical Society
Time Inc. Time Research Center Files
1919-2015
New-York Historical Society
Time, inc.
MS 3009-RG 13
1592 Linear feet (1592 boxes which includes 582 reels of microfilm)
The Time Research Center Files contain research materials collected by Time Inc. reporters, researchers, and library staff in the main areas of Bio Files, Presidents Files, and Subject Files along with microfilmed news cables that had been pulled from older versions of these files. Many of the files originally belonged to a Time Inc. reference library known throughout the years as The Morgue, The Bureau of Editorial Reference, and The Editorial Reference Library.
Arrangement Note
The record group is currently organized in five series:
Series I. Bio Files
Series II. Presidents Files
Series III. Subject Files
Series IV. Microfilm of Time-Life News Service Correspondent Wires
Series V. Administrative Files
Historical Note
The files from the Time Research Center originally belonged to a Time Inc. library known throughout the years as The Morgue, The Bureau of Editorial Reference, and The Editorial Reference Library. It seems like the library existed longest as The Editorial Reference Library, and most staff referred to it as "Edit Ref". The library maintained research materials that reporters and researchers from all magazines used when writing articles. Editorial Services managed the library along with the Picture Collection (later called the Life Picture Collection), Archives (beginning in the mid-1990s), the Index Department (closed in 1994 or 1995), and the Photo Lab.
The files were built over the years from the various magazines' Carbon Files. A Carbon File was created by a reporter for every article that ran in a Time Inc. magazine, comprising all the collected research, and retained by that magazine for around 14 months before being turned over to the Editorial Reference Library. There the contents were distributed into the Bio, Subject or Company Files. Library staff also added additional clippings to the files. The bulk of the Company Files were sent to an offsite storage facility and lost in a series of storage facility arsons in the mid-1990s.
Time Warner closed The Editorial Reference Library in 2001 after the AOL merger failure. At this time, staff culled the files and sent some to the smaller libraries funded by individual magazines. Business and finance subjects went to the Business Information Research Center, a library used by Money and Fortune, and Fortune still maintains these files. Entertainment industry subjects went to the People Research Center, and these files later were acquired by the LAC Group. Files not culled or sent to another library became property of the newly created Time Research Center housed in offsite storage.
Citations:
Bill Hooper, email message to Holly Deakyne, 6 July 2016.
Bill Hooper, email message to Holly Deakyne, 25 August 2016.
Bill Hooper, email message to Holly Deakyne, 15 May 2017.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers with the exception of restricted materials. Restricted materials may include medical records and records with personally identifiable information. Unreformatted digital material in the collection is not accessible. Restricted boxes include R27. Items with preservation issues are also listed as restricted and may be available for use upon request after further Conservation review. These materials are in boxes R20-R22, R28, and 2785. The majority of materials are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use. The index to the microfilm is stored onsite.
Related Archival Materials Note
This finding aid relates to just one record group of the Time Inc. Records. For information about the other record groups and for overall information about the archives, please see the Guide to the Time Inc. Records (MS 3009). The Henry Luce Papers (MS 3014) were acquired with the Time Inc. Records. The collection of books acquired with the records are cataloged as the Time Inc. Reference Library.
Scope and Contents Note
The Time Inc. Time Research Center Files contain research materials used by reporters and researchers at various magazines across Time Inc. The files are in four main series of Bio Files, Presidents Files, Subject Files, and Microfilm with smaller series of Administrative Files containing guides and manuals for Time Research Center staff and users of the reference materials in the library.
The majority of research and reference materials are magazine and newspaper clippings. Other types of material include telegrams and other correspondence, correspondent dispatches, transcripts of interviews and speeches, editorial outlines for articles, editorial policies, press releases, and drafts of articles. Microfilm contains reels created by the The Editorial Reference Library during a major imaging project in the mid-1960s mainly of raw reporting and dispatches from correspondents. The reels also contain the only examples of the destroyed Company Files which were lost in fires.
According to the deed of gift transferring the archive to the New-York Historical Society, "Most of what survives of Time Inc. correspondent cables and raw reportage in hard copy format" is in the Bio Files and Subject Files of this record group. The deed may also mean the material on the microfilm reels.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Time Inc. in 2015.
Other Finding Aids
The folder list in Series III. Subject Files has been condensed to facilitate ease of use. Please use the condensed finding aid to make box requests. The detailed folder list for Series III. Subject Files is located here.
Biographies (documents); Clippings (information artifacts); Corporation records.; Corporations -- History.; Corporations -- New York (State) -- New York.; Dispatches; Organization files.; Pamphlets.; Presidents -- United States.; Press releases.; Publishers and publishing -- New York (State) -- New York.; Reporters and reporting -- United States.; Research libraries.; Telegrams.; Transcripts.; Time, inc. -- Archives; Time, inc. -- History
- Series I. Bio Files, 1919-2015; 390.66 Linear feet (391 boxes)
  Scope and Contents Note
  The Bio Files contains materials regarding notable cultural and political figures collected and used for research by various Time Inc. publications. Astronauts, athletes, scientists, artists, photographers, journalists, orchestra conductors, composers, business leaders, historical figures, authors, Supreme Court justices, mobsters, religious leaders, military figures, royalty, persons of interest, and politicians both American and foreign are included.
  The majority of the files contain newspaper and magazine clippings. Files also contain telegrams, bureau reports, internal and external correspondence, article correction forms, biographical overviews, press releases, exhibition materials, and letters to the editor.
  Arrangement Note
  Based on the original organizational scheme, files are organized alphabetically by name; some files are labeled using married names, chosen names, or titles. If multiple folders exist for the same name, chronological order is used. Some names are further organized by subheaders Sketches and Speeches.
  - -A-
    - Aalto, Alvar, 1960-1986 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 1)
    - Abalkin, Leonid Ivanovich, 1991 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 2)
    - Abbado, Claudio, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 3)
    - Abbas, Ferhat, 1958-1966 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 4-5)
    - Abbe, Ernst, 1958-1968 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 6)
    - Abbey, Edward, 1984-1991 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 7)
    - Abbott Family, 1973 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 8)
    - Abbott, Jack Henry, 1981 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 9)
    - Abbot, Robert S., 1933 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 10)
    - Abd-El-Krim, 1947-1963 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 11)
    - Abdel-Rahman, Sheik Omar, 1993 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 12)
    - Abe, Kobo, 1966-1991 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 13)
    - Abel, Alan, 1966-1971 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 14)
    - Abel, Rudolf Ivanovich, 1961-1985 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 15)
    - Abel, Irowith Wilbur, 1975 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 16)
    - Abernathy, Ralph David, 1968-1987 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 17)
    - Abouhalima, Mahmud, 1993 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 18)
    - Abourezk, James, 1973 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 19)
    - Abplanalp, Robert H., 1970 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 20)
    - Abraham (Biblical character), 1955-1966 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 21)
    - Abram, Morris B., 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 794, Folder 22)
    - Abrams, Creighton Jr., 1945-1975 (Offsite-box 794)
    - Abrams, Creighton Jr., 1945-1975 (Offsite-box 795)
    - Abrams, Charles, 1971 (Offsite-box 795, Folder 5)
    - Abrams, Elliot, 1984 (Offsite-box 795, Folder 6)
    - Abrams, Floyd, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 795, Folder 7)
    - Abrams, Harry N., 1962-1979 (Offsite-box 795, Folder 8)
    - Abrams, Robert, 1975-1986 (Offsite-box 795, Folder 9)
    - Abravanel, Maurice, 1970-1986 (Offsite-box 795, Folder 10)
    - Abs, Hermann Josef, 1960-1969 (Offsite-box 795, Folder 11)
    - Abt, John J., 1950-1991 (Offsite-box 795, Folder 12)
    - Abzug, Bella S., 1973-1986 (Offsite-box 795, Folder 13)
    - Accardo, Tony ("Big Tuna"), 1959-1987 (Offsite-box 795, Folder 14)
    - Acheson, Dean Gooderham, 1953-1986 (Offsite-box 795)
    - Acheson, Dean Gooderham, 1953-1986 (Offsite-box 796)
    - Ackerman, Diane, 1986-1992 (Offsite-box 796, Folder 2)
    - Ackley, Gardner, 1961-1968 (Offsite-box 796, Folder 3)
    - Acosta, Bert, 1976 (Offsite-box 796, Folder 4)
    - Acton, Baron, 1957-1982 (Offsite-box 796, Folder 5)
    - Adamic, Louis, 1932-1976 (Offsite-box 796, Folder 6)
    - Adams, Brockman, 1976 (Offsite-box 796, Folder 7)
    - Adams, Charles Francis, 1930-1961 (Offsite-box 796, Folder 8)
    - Adams, Evangline, 1930-1961 (Offsite-box 796, Folder 9)
    - Adams, Franklin Pierce, 1935-1961 (Offsite-box 796, Folder 10)
    - Adams, Gerry, 1988-1993 (Offsite-box 796, Folder 11)
    - Adams, Henry, 1963-1986 (Offsite-box 796, Folder 12-14)
    - Adams, John Bodkin, 1957-1962 (Offsite-box 796, Folder 15)
    - Adams, Randall Dale, 1989 (Offsite-box 796, Folder 16)
    - Adams, Robert McCormack, 1967-1989 (Offsite-box 796, Folder 17)
    - Adams, Samuel, 1960-1976 (Offsite-box 796, Folder 18)
    - Adams, Samuel A., 1975-1988 (Offsite-box 796, Folder 19)
    - Adams, Samuel Hopkins, 1955-1963 (Offsite-box 796, Folder 20)
    - Adams, Sherman, 1965-1993 (Offsite-box 797, Folder 1-3)
    - Adams, Theodore Floyd, 1956-1980 (Offsite-box 797, Folder 4-6)
    - Adams, Thomas, 1966-1974 (Offsite-box 797, Folder 7)
    - Ade, George, 1961-1986 (Offsite-box 797, Folder 8)
    - Adenauer, Konrad, 1949-1973 (Offsite-box 797)
    - Adenauer, Konrad, 1949-1973 (Offsite-box 798)
    - Adham, Kamal, 1975-1996 (Offsite-box 798, Folder 3)
    - Adham, Kamal [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Offsite-box R27, Folder 1)
    - Adler, Alfred, 1932-1986 (Offsite-box 798, Folder 4)
    - Adler, Alfred [RESTRICTED], 1932-1986 (Offsite-box R27)
      1 computer disc (floppy disk): 3 1/2 in.
    - Adler, Felix, 1935-1975 (Offsite-box 798, Folder 5)
    - Adler, Kurt Herbert, 1957-1988 (Offsite-box 798, Folder 6)
    - Adler, Mortimer Jerome, 1967-1985 (Offsite-box 798, Folder 7-8)
    - Adler, Polly, 1953-1962 (Offsite-box 798, Folder 9)
    - Adzehubei, Aleksei I., 1962-1965 (Offsite-box 798, Folder 10)
    - Adzhubei, Madam Aleksei, 1957-1993 (Offsite-box 798, Folder 11)
    - Agam, Yaacov (Jacob), 1967-1983 (Offsite-box 798, Folder 12)
    - Aganbegian, Abel G., 1974-1988 (Offsite-box 798, Folder 13)
    - Agassiz, Louis, 19363-1987 (Offsite-box 798, Folder 14)
    - Agca, Mehmet Ali, 1981-1991 (Offsite-box 798, Folder 15)
    - Agee, Joel, 1980-1988 (Offsite-box 798, Folder 16)
    - Agee, Philip B., 1975-1980 (Offsite-box 798, Folder 17)
    - Ageloff, Sylvia, 1940-1959 (Offsite-box 798, Folder 18)
    - Aggett, Neil, 1982 (Offsite-box 798, Folder 19)
    - Agnew Family, 1969-1986 (Offsite-box 798, Folder 20)
    - Agnew, Harold, 1967-1985 (Offsite-box 798, Folder 21)
    - Agnew, Spiro Theodore, 1968-1991 (Offsite-box 799, Folder 1-10)
    - Agnew, Mrs. Spiro Theodore (Judy), 1968 (Offsite-box 799, Folder 11)
    - Agnon, Shmuel Yosef, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 799, Folder 12)
    - Agnos, Art, 1987-1992 (Offsite-box 799, Folder 13)
    - Agron, Salvatore, 1959-1977 (Offsite-box 799, Folder 14)
    - Aguilar, Andres, 1979-1988 (Offsite-box 799, Folder 15)
    - Aguilanaldo, Emilio, 1932-1967 (Offsite-box 799, Folder 16)
    - Ahearne, John F., 1972-1992 (Offsite-box 800, Folder 1)
    - Ahmad, Eqbal, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 800, Folder 2)
    - Ahmanson, Howard F., 1957-1968 (Offsite-box 800, Folder 3)
    - Ahmed, Fakharuddin ALi, 1966-1977 (Offsite-box 800, Folder 4)
    - Aiken, Conrad, 1953-1986 (Offsite-box 800, Folder 5)
    - Aiken, George David, 1938-1985 (Offsite-box 800, Folder 6)
    - Ait-Ahmed, Hocine, 1958-1985 (Offsite-box 800, Folder 7)
    - Aitmatov, Chingiz, 1975-1991 (Offsite-box 800, Folder 9)
    - Akbar (the Great), Emperor, 1962-1991 (Offsite-box 800, Folder 10)
    - Akeley, Carl Ehran, 1963-1980 (Offsite-box 800, Folder 11)
    - Akhenaten, Pharoah of Egypt, 1960-1976 (Offsite-box 800, Folder 12)
    - Akhmadulina, Bella, 1936-1972 (Offsite-box 800, Folder 13)
    - Akhmatova, Anna, 1966-1988 (Offsite-box 800, Folder 14)
    - Aksenov, Vasily, 1966-1988 (Offsite-box 800, Folder 15)
    - Akutagawa, Ryunosuke, 1938-1988 (Offsite-box 800, Folder 16)
    - Alanbrooke, Viscount, 1940-1957 (Offsite-box 800, Folder 17)
    - Alarcon, Ricardo, 1960-1993 (Offsite-box 800, Folder 18)
    - Albee, Edward Franklin, 1929-1965 (Offsite-box 800, Folder 19)
    - Albert, Carl, 1965-1988 (Offsite-box 800)
    - Albert, Carl, 1965-1988 (Offsite-box 801)
    - Albert, Stephen, 1985-1992 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 3)
    - Albertazzie, Ralph D., 1969-1985 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 4)
    - Albertson, William, 1959-1965 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 5)
    - Albertz, Heinrich, 1959-1993 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 6)
    - Aleizu, Pedro, 1932-1965 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 7)
    - Albrechy, Susanne, 1977-1990 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 8)
    - Albright twins (Ivan and Malvin), 1934-1947 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 9)
    - Albright, Ivan de Lorraine, 1939-1983 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 10)
    - Alcala, Zamora, 1930-1946 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 12)
    - Alch, Gerald, 1969-1974 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 13)
    - Alcock, George, 1983 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 14)
    - Alcock, Sir John William, 1938-1988 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 15)
    - Alden family, 1941-1991 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 16)
    - Alden, John & Priscilla, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 17)
    - Alderman, Willie Isreal, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 18)
    - Alderisio, Felix Antonion, 1961-1966 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 19)
    - Aldington, Mrs. Richard (Hilda Doolittle), 1961-1984 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 20)
    - Aldington, Richard, 1940-1962 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 21)
    - Aldrich, Alexander, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 22)
    - Aldrich, Arnold D., 1961-1984 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 23)
    - Aldrich, Nelson Wilmarth, 1935-1964 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 24)
    - Aldrich, Richard Seere, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 801, Folder 25)
    - Aldridge, John W., 1962-1992 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 1)
    - Aldrin, Edwin E., 1969-1974 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 2)
    - Aldrin, Edwin E., Jr. (Buzz), 1979-1989 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 3)
    - Alechinsky, Pierre, 1965-1975 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 4)
    - Aleixandre, Vicente, 1977-1984 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 5)
    - Alexsandrov, Anatoly P., 1975-1984 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 6)
    - Alekseyeva, Yelizaveta, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 7)
    - Aleman, Jose, 1978 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 8)
    - Aleman, Miguel, 1943-1985 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 9)
    - Alemann, Roberto Teodoro, 1962 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 10)
    - Alessandri, Jorge, 1958-1973 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 11)
    - Alex, Gus, 1968-1986 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 12)
    - Alexander the Great, King of Macedonia, 1930-1989 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 13-14)
    - Alexander, Czar of Russia, 1965-1992 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 15)
    - Alexander II, Czar of Russia, 1963-1977 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 16)
    - Alexander III, Czar of Russia, 1966-1988 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 17)
    - Alexander of Hillsborough, Earl, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 18)
    - Alexander II, of Yugoslavia, 1974-1992 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 19)
    - Alexander, Dan Dale, 1956-1960 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 20)
    - Alexander, Donald C., 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 21)
    - Alexander, Franx Gabriel, 1964-1978 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 22)
    - Alexander, Grand Duke of Russia, 1931-1984 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 23)
    - Alexander, Henry Clay, 1959-1969 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 24)
    - Alexander, Herbert E., 1968-1988 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 25)
    - Alexander, Kelly M., 1968-1986 (Offsite-box 802, Folder 26)
    - Alexander, Sandy Fraser, 1970-1985 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 1)
    - Alexanderson, Ernist Frederick, 1938-1975 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 2)
    - Alexei, Patriarch, 1950-1970 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 3)
    - Alfaro, Richardo J., 1932-1971 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 4)
    - Alfieri, Oduardo Dino, 1937-1961 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 5)
    - Alfonsin, Raul, 1983-1989 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 6)
    - Alfrink, Bernard Jan, 1962-1987 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 7)
    - Alfven, Hannes, 1960-1970 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 8)
    - Algren, Nelson, 1942-1992 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 9)
    - Ali, Mohamad (Pakistani Prime Minister, 1955-1956), 1956-1989 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 10)
    - Ali, Mohamad (Pakistani Prime Minister, 1953-1955), 1962-1987 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 11)
    - Alia, Ramiz, 1962-1992 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 12)
    - Alinsky, Saul David, 1961-1989 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 13-14)
    - Alioto, Joseph, 1969-1972 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 15)
    - Allais, Maurice, 1988 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 16)
    - Allcard, Edward C., 1941-1960 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 17)
    - Alleg, Henri, 1953-1960 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 18)
    - Allegro, John Marc, 1960-1970 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 19)
    - Allen, Asa A., 1970-1982 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 20)
    - Allen, Arthur A., 1939-1968 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 21)
    - Allen, Edmund Turney, 1939-1943 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 22)
    - Allne, Ethan, 1954-1976 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 23)
    - Allen, George Edward, 1936-1973 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 24)
    - Allen, George N., 1936-1973 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 25)
    - Allen, Hervey, 1942-1952 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 26)
    - Allen, George Venable, 1946-1975 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 27)
    - Allen, Ivan, 1961-1969 (Offsite-box 803, Folder 28)
    - Allen, James B., 1972-1978 (Offsite-box 804, Folder 1)
    - Allen, Jimmy Lee, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 804, Folder 2)
    - Allen, Joseph Percival, IV, 1982-1988 (Offsite-box 804, Folder 3)
    - Allen, Lew, Jr., 1970-1990 (Offsite-box 804, Folder 4)
    - Allen, Richard V., 1982-1987 (Offsite-box 804, Folder 5)
    - Allen, Robert S., 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 804, Folder 6)
    - Allen, Mrs. Vivian Beaumont, 1962-1967 (Offsite-box 804, Folder 7)
    - Allen, Robert G., 1980-1986 (Offsite-box 804, Folder 8)
    - Allen, Terry (de la Mesa), 1943-1985 (Offsite-box 804, Folder 9)
    - Allen, Walter, 1961-1965 (Offsite-box 804, Folder 10)
    - Allen, William, 1932-1965 (Offsite-box 804, Folder 11)
    - Allen, William H., 1930-1963 (Offsite-box 804, Folder 12)
    - Allenby, Viscount, 1933-1936 (Offsite-box 804, Folder 13)
    - Allende Family, 1970-1977 (Offsite-box 804, Folder 14)
    - Allende (Gossens), Salvador, 1962-1988 (Offsite-box 804, Folder 15-23)
    - Allers, Franz, 1960-1971 (Offsite-box 804, Folder 24)
    - Alley, Rewi, 1940-1941 (Offsite-box 804, Folder 25)
    - Allgood, Clarence W., 1961-1969 (Offsite-box 804, Folder 26)
    - Alligood, Clarence Thomas, 1975-1977 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 1)
    - Alliluyev Family, 1967 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 2)
    - Allin, John Maury, 1973-1987 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 3)
    - Allingham, Maury, 1949-1989 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 4)
    - Allison, Dorothy, 1979-1981 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 5)
    - Allison, Graham, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 6)
    - Alloway, Lawrence, 1957-1976 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 7)
    - Allred, Gloria, 1977-1988 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 8)
    - Allport, Gordon Willard, 1954-1979 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 9)
    - Allred, James B., 1961-1966 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 10)
    - Allred, Rulon C., 1970-1977 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 11)
    - Allyn, Stanley Charles, 1957-1960 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 12)
    - Almirante, Giorgio, 1946-1988 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 13)
    - Almond, Edward Mallory, 1946-1950 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 14)
    - Almond, James Lindsay, Jr., 1957-1962 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 15-16)
    - Aloni, Shulamit, 1959-1992 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 17)
    - Alpert, Jane Lauren, 1969-1993 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 18)
    - Alpert, Richard, 1957-1986 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 19)
    - Alphand, Herve, 1957-1970 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 20)
    - Alphand, Nicole, 1958-1979 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 21-23)
    - Alsogaray, Alvaro Carlos, 1953-1960 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 24)
    - Alsop, Joseph Wright, Jr., 1966-1989 (Offsite-box 805, Folder 25)
    - Alsop, Stewart, 1947-1993 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 1)
    - Alsop, Susan Mary, 1963-1991 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 2)
    - Altgeld, John Peter, 1941-1966 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 3)
    - Alther, Lisa, 1976-1990 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 4)
    - Althusser, Louis, 1980-1990 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 5)
    - Altman, Benjamin, 1966-1977 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 6)
    - Altman, Lawrence K., 1977-1981 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 7)
    - Altman, Stuart H., 1974-1993 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 8)
    - Altrincham, (2nd) Baron, 1957-1986 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 9)
    - Altschul, Selig, 1960-1992 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 10)
    - Alunni, Carrado, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 11)
    - Alvarado, Anthony J., 1983-1987 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 12)
    - Alvarez, A., 1966-1982 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 13)
    - Alvarez, Everett, 1964-1991 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 14)
    - Alvarez (Martinez), Gustavo, 1984-1993 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 15)
    - Alvarez (Del Vayo), Julio, 1939-1973 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 16)
    - Alvarez, Luis Walter, 1959-1989 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 14)
    - Alvarez, Walter, 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 18)
    - Alvarez, Walter Clement, 1957-1978 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 19)
    - Amalrik, Andrei Alekseyevich, 1970-1980 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 20)
    - Almalrik, Mrs. Andrei Alekseyevich, 1969-1980 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 21)
    - Amalu, Sam, 1962 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 22)
    - Amann, Max, 1933-1967 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 23)
    - Amati, Nicolo, 1960-1981 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 24)
    - Ambartsumyan, Victor A., 1961-1971 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 25)
    - Ambedkar, Bhimrao Ramji, 1936-1968 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 26)
    - Ameling, Elly, 1980-1986 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 27)
    - Amer, Abdel Hakim, 1960-1967 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 28)
    - Amerson, Lucius Davenport, 1966-1971 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 29)
    - Amery, John, 1941-1966 (Offsite-box 839, Folder 30)
    - Amery, Julian, 1956-1986 (Offsite-box 840, Folder 1)
    - Amery, Leopold Stennett, 1941-1965 (Offsite-box 840, Folder 2)
    - Ames, Adelbert, Jr., 1934-1969 (Offsite-box 840, Folder 3)
    - Ames, Amyas, 1965-1976 (Offsite-box 840, Folder 4)
    - Ames, Bruce N., 1975-1992 (Offsite-box 840, Folder 5)
    - Amichai, Yehuda, 1966-1992 (Offsite-box 840, Folder 6)
    - Amin, Ali, 1974-1960 (Offsite-box 840, Folder 7)
    - Amin, Hafisullah, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 840, Folder 8)
    - Amin, Idi, 1976-1982 (Offsite-box 840, Folder 9-11)
    - Amini, Ali, 1962-1978 (Offsite-box 840, Folder 12)